<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HamsterCare</string>
    <string name="default_hamster_name">Hammy</string>

    <string name="contactUs">
        Email: kwali5ying@gmail.com
        \nPhone: +65 90100463
        \nLocation: Singapore University of Technology and Design
        \n          8 Somapah Rd, Singapore 487372
    </string>

    <string name="version">
        HamsterCare v1.1
        \nCredits to Professors Norman Lee and Cheung Ngai-Mann for their guidance and support
    </string>

    <string name="helpBottomNav">
        The bottom navigation bar allows movement between the primary functions in the app.
        \nIt is split into 3 tabs - Feed, Photo and Help (from left to right).
    </string>

    <string name="feedTab">
        Topping up food and water is done here.
        \nThe left column displays information about the previous top-up of food, the amount of
        food left, and allows the top-up of food through the \"Feed Me Food!\" button.
        \nThe right column displays information about the previous top-up of water, the amount of
        water left, and allows the top-up of water through the \"Feed Me Water!\" button.
        \nAt the bottom, automatic topping-up of food and water is enabled/disabled by toggling the
        switch on/off.
    </string>

    <string name="photoTab">
        You can take a picture of your hamster at any point of time to see how it is doing.
        \nSimply do so through the \"Snap A Picture!\" button.
    </string>

    <string name="settingsTab">
        Set/Change your hamster\'s name and/or profile picture here.
        \nClick on the blue button with an arrow to choose an image:
        \n  1. Use our default hamster profile picture
        \n  2. Upload an image from your phone gallery
        \n  3. Take a photo with your phone camera
        \n  4. Use the latest HamsterCare photo taken in the Photo Tab
        \nClick the green button with a tick to confirm changes for both name and profile picture.
    </string>
</resources>
